<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Agency on Adam Faryna</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Agency on Adam Faryna</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://adamfaryna.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cookie Policy</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/cookie-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/cookie-policy/</guid><description>Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 21:55:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/terms-of-service/</guid><description>General This website (the “Site”) is owned and operated by Appdy d/b/a “adamfaryna.com ” (“COMPANY,” “we” or “us”). By using the Site, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service and to use the Site in accordance with these Terms of Service, our Privacy Policy and any additional terms and conditions that may apply to specific sections of the Site or to products and services available through the Site or from COMPANY.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their “Personally identifiable information” (PII) is being used online. PI is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Business Proposals</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/proposals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/proposals/</guid><description>If you have any proposals, either service or product that you want to offer to us, please use the form below to contact us.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t send multiple submissions about the same product or service. It will only leave a poor impression of you and your business. Single submission is enough for us to notice your business.
If we find your offer interesting we will contact you shortly.
Thank you</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/contact/</guid><description>If you want to contact us to learn more about our services, please use the contact form below. We will reply to you shortly.
You can also call us &amp;#43;44 7561399765 .
If you want to offer us your product or service please use the dedicated page for business proposals. Contact information on this page is for clients and people interested in our services only. Keep in mind that ignoring this notice, and contacting us regardless to offer us your products or services, will leave a permanently poor impression of both your ethic and your business.</description></item><item><title>Facebook Ads Expert</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/career/facebook-ads-expert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/career/facebook-ads-expert/</guid><description>We are looking for a talented Facebook Ads specialist to join our team.
We don&amp;rsquo;t care how old are you, where you are from, what are your personal preferences, or what drives you. We want to cultivate a respective work place, where professional attitude matters the most. The only thing we care about is if you can take a job and deliver.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to have plenty of experience (but that helps).</description></item><item><title>Free Marketing Audit</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/free-audit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/free-audit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/portfolio/</guid><description/></item><item><title>SEO Expert</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/career/seo-expert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/career/seo-expert/</guid><description>We are looking for a talented SEO specialist to join our team.
We don&amp;rsquo;t care how old are you, where you are from, what are your personal preferences, or what drives you. We want to cultivate a respective work place, where professional attitude matters the most. The only thing we care about is if you can take a job and deliver.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to have plenty of experience (but that helps).</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/services/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Web Designer</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/career/web-designer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/career/web-designer/</guid><description>We are looking for a talented Web Designer to join our team.
We don&amp;rsquo;t care how old are you, where you are from, what are your personal preferences, or what drives you. We want to cultivate a respective work place, where professional attitude matters the most. The only thing we care about is if you can take a job and deliver.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to have plenty of experience (but that helps).</description></item><item><title>Wordpress Developer</title><link>https://adamfaryna.com/career/web-developer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamfaryna.com/career/web-developer/</guid><description>We are looking for a talented Web Developer to join our team.
We don&amp;rsquo;t care how old are you, where you are from, what are your personal preferences, or what drives you. We want to cultivate a respective workplace, where professional attitude matters the most. The only thing we care about is if you can take a job and deliver.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to have plenty of experience (but that helps).</description></item></channel></rss>